It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
To help troubled villagers, Senhime's group fought against and took down Yamata no Orochi under Shutentiger's cotrol.
난처한 상황에 처한 마을 사람들을 돕기 위해 센히메 일행은 슈텐타이거가 조종하는 야마타노오로치하고 싸워 쓰러뜨렸다.
And Musashi managed to obtain Tenkūmaru, hidden inside Yamata no Orochi.
그리고 무사시는 야마타노오로치가 숨기고 있던 천구환을 손에 넣는 데 성공했다.
By this, he is one step closer to the mastery of the technique of dual blades.
이것으로 이도류 완성에 한 보 더 다가간 것이다.
The Ultimate Thief of
금으로 번쩍이는 도둑, 고에몬도이오
Damned Musashi and Kojirō...
네이놈, 무사시, 코지로 놈.
Is Goemondo not in touch yet?
어이, 고에몬도하고 아직 연락은 닿지 않는가.
T- that's... we did everything we could, but he still is out of reach.
그, 그게... 모든 방법을 썼지만 아직 연락이 닿지 않습니다.
That lazy...
그 녀석...
Countless times have I told him to give it his all on the job...
몇번이고 성실하게 임무에 임하라고 말했을 텐데...
Contact Goemondo no matter the cost!
어떻게든 고에몬도하고 연락이 닿게 만들어라!
Yessir!
예!
Meanwhile, Musashi's group was in mountain around Yamagata.
그 쯤, 무사시 일행은 야마가타 가까이 있는 산중에 있었다.
Who is it-dasu?
누구시오?
It's me!
나야!
Osenchan! Don't interrupt me like that-dasu!
오센짱! 방해하면 곤란하오!
But I'm bored.
그래도 지루한걸.
Hey! I am not playing-dasu!
저기! 나, 놀고 있는 게 아니오!
I was training to develop the technique of dual blades-dasu!
이도류를 고안하기 위해 필사적으로 연구하고 있던 참이오!
If you want someone to play with that much, then go play with Kojirō-dasu!
그렇게 놀 상대를 원하면 코지로하고 놀면 되오!
No way! Kojirō's always too serious and he's no fun.
싫어! 코지로는 너무 진지해서 재미없어.
Alright. This rotation is just right.
음, 역시 이 정도로 휘두르는 게 제일이다.
Hey, if you're not going to play, then let's get out of the mountain as soon as possible.
있잖아, 놀 거 아니라면 빨리 산 밖으로 나가자.
But I have to train my technique of dual blades...
그래도 나 이도류를...
Can't you hear me? Then I'll ask my grandpa to decapitate you!
내 말이 안 들려? 그럼 할아버지한테 부탁해서 참수시켜버린다!
T- that's... All right-dasu.
그, 그건... 알겠소.
Hey, you people over there.
어이, 거기 당신들.
What are you doing here?
그런 곳에서 뭘 하고 있는가.
To train my sword skills-dasu.
검의 수행이오.
Train your sword skills? That sounds suspicious. Get them!
검의 수행? 수상한 놈이군. 잡아라!
What a handsome man!
어라, 잘 생긴 남자잖아.
Osenchan, get back-dasu!
오센짱, 위험하오!
It's cowardly to rush at me all of sudden-dasu! That leaves me no choice but to get rid of all those sparks jumping to me-dasu.
갑자기 달려들다니 비겁하오! 이렇게 된 바 달려드는 불꽃은 전부 제거할 뿐이오.
Yielding such a suspicious thing also must be telling that you're working for Goemondo.
수상한 물건을 가지고 있다니 역시 고에몬도의 동료겠군.
Who is Goemondo-dasu?
고에몬도라니 누구이오?
Easy thing-dasu!
쉽소!
Kojirō!
코지로!
More comrades?
또 동료가 있다는 것인가...
You saved me-dasu!
덕분에 살았소!
Musashi, you are not desperate enough! You are never opening your eyes to dual blades at that rate!
무사시, 넌 충분히 필사적이지 못하다! 그따위로 해서 이도류를 개안하는 일 따위가 될 것 같냐!
What did you say-dasu?!
뭣이오?!
Chink in the armor!
빈틈이다!
Please wait. While I am not sure about what was going on, but we swear that we do nothing suspicious.
기다려 주십시오. 무슨 일이 있는지는 모르지만 저희는 절대 수상한 자가 아닙니다.
I do not intend to be fooled over such lie!
그런 거짓말에 넘어갈 생각은 없다!
Let me settle this!
끝장내 주겠다!
Stop! Freeze!
그만하라!
I am Senhime, the granddaughter of General Ieyasu, the ruler of Kantō, the number one of Jipangu!
이 나를 누구라고 생각하는가. 지팡구 넘버 원의 관동을 지배하는 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀, 센히메이다!
You are being impudent! Lower your heads!
에이! 건방지다! 허리를 숙여라!
Yessir!
예!
I am not going to make excuses on our grave discourtesy.
변명하지 않겠습니다. 말도 안 되는 실례를!
Alright, alright! You can straighten yourself.
알았어, 알았어! 이제 됐으니까 몸 펴.
But still, why did you attack us?
그래도 어째서 저희를 덮쳤습니까.
We confused with Goemondo's clan.
그게, 고에몬도 일당으로 착각했습니다.
Who is Goemondo-dasu?
그 고에몬도라는 자는 어떤 자이오?
He is a grand thief who tries to plunder this Yamagata castle and bring chaos.
이 야마가타 성을 약탈하고 혼란에 빠뜨리려 하는 대도둑입니다. 고에몬도는 신출귀몰은 물론이고 검술 실력도 터무니없이 좋습니다.
Moreover, it is impossible to catch him because of the giant centipede he controls.
게다가 거대한 지네를 조종해서 잡는 것이 불가능합니다.
Not only Goemondo flatters himself all the time, but also he's shameless!
쉽게 기분이 오락가락하는 고에몬도는 뻔뻔하기까지!
(鯱: Shachihoko, an ornament with a form of mythical carp with the head of a lion and the body of a fish)
(鯱: 샤치호코, 성곽 등의 용마루 양단에 장식해 놓는, 머리는 호랑이 같고 등에는 가시가 돋친 곤두선 물고기 모양의 장식물)
This time, he sent an advance notice that he'll steal the gold ornament at the top of our Yamagata castle.
이번엔 우리 야마가타 성 지붕의 금장식을 훔치겠다고 예고장을 보내 왔습니다.
Today is the day of that notice, but it's not like we can handle that.
예고한 시기는 오늘 밤. 그러나 이러지도 저러지도 못하고 있습니다.
I was trying to catch Goemondo as the leader, but...
직접 진두에 서서 고에몬도를 잡으려고 하고 있으나...
So that's why you confused us as Goemondo's comrades-dasu.
그래서 우릴 고에몬도의 동료로 잘못 생각했던 것이오.
It's inexcusable.
대단히 죄송합니다.
That ornament is the symbol of our Yamagata family. We wouldn't worth to live anymore if it gets stolen.
그 장식은 우리 야마가타 가의 심볼입니다. 그것을 도둑맞아서는 저희 일족은 더 이상 살아있을 수 없게 됩니다.
I can't let a pretty man cry.
미남자를 울게 둘 수는 없어.
-Musashi! Kojirō! Help them get Goemondo! -Alright.
-무사시! 코지로! 고에몬도를 잡는 걸 도와! -예.
So many people are standing guard! Not even a grand thief will manage to steal these-dasu.
이렇게나 많은 사람이 지키고 있으면 아무리 대도둑이라고 해도 훔치는 건 무리겠소.
But that does not mean that you can let your guards down.
그래도 처음부터 끝까지 주의해야 한다는 말도 있다.
Kojirō!
코지로!
Huh?
어?
Probably toilet-dasu...
화장실일까나...
Finally we're alone together, Shunnosuke.
드디어 둘이서만 있게 되었네요, 슌노스케 님.
B- but I must keep doing my guard duties...
그, 그래도, 저는 경비를 해야...
You can leave them to Musashi and Kojirō.
그런 건 무사시하고 코지로한테 맡기면 돼요.
But, Senhime...
그래도, 센히메 님...
Don't be so formal; call me Osenchan!
그런 딱딱한 말 하지 말고, 오센짱이라 불러 봐요.
S- Osenchan?
오- 오센짱입니까.
More gently.
더 상냥하게 불러줘.
Osenchan!
오센짱!
Perfect.
오, 좋아.
You are destroying the mood of a while!
모처럼의 분위기를 부수냐!
Hey, Kojirō!
잠깐, 코지로!
What are you playing with over there?
너 거기서 뭘 하고 놀고 있는 거야?
No, I am not playing. We were making those.
아니, 저는 놀고 있는 것이 아닙니다. 저것을 만들고 있습니다.
I see. You were making substitutes.
그렇군요. 가짜를 만들고 있었군요.
Mr. Shunnosuke, you have a good insight.
역시 슌노스케 님. 통찰이 빠르시군요.
You're one pretty man with a good brain!
미남자, 머리도 잘 돌아가네!
I wonder what is Otsuru doing-dasu...
오쯔루 뭐하고 있을지 궁금하오...
She should be sleeping well by now-dasu.
이미 잘 자고 있을 것이오.
I want to have Otsuru's rice balls-dasu!
오쯔루가 만들어주는 주먹밥이 먹고 싶소!
It got cold suddenly... and I need to go to toilet-dasu. I can't hold-dasu!
갑자기 추워졌소. 그리고 화장실 가고 싶어졌소. 참을 수 없소!
Let's hurry up and replace with the real one.
자, 서둘러서 진품하고 교체하자.
This is a privy. In other word, a toilet.
여긴 변소. 그러니까, 화장실이다.
I'm relieved-dasu.
속이 시원하오.
Huh? Why are there the ornaments from the roof-dasu?
어라? 이런 곳에 어째서 지붕의 금장식이 있는 것이오?
That's it! I know what to do-dasu!
그렇소! 뭘 할지 생각났소!
It's time.
예고한 시간이다.
Kojirō, did the replacing go well?
코지로, 바꿔치는 건 잘 됐어?
Yes. It's perfectly done.
예. 확실하게 해 두었습니다.
Lord, Goemondo might gave up stealing from all these guards we posted!
영주님, 고에몬도 놈, 이만큼의 경비를 보고 포기한 것일지도요!
I do hope so.
음, 그러면 좋겠다만.
Hey! Do not run away! Fight!
어이! 달아나지 마라! 싸워라!
No, this is a bait!
안 돼, 이건 미끼다.
Musashi! Do not let your guards down!
무사시! 방심하지 마라!
Goemondo, where are you coming from-dasu?!
고에몬도 놈, 어디서 올 셈이오!
I'll take you down at once-dasu!
해치워 주겠소!
Goemondo
고에몬도
What a sightly sight! I am Goemondo, the number one grand thief of Jipangu!
절경이군, 절경이야! 지팡구 넘버원의 대도둑, 고에몬도!
As I gave notice, I am here to take that gold ornament!
예고한 대로 그 금장식 가져가러 납셨다!
Coming from the sky is cowardly-dasu!
하늘에서 오다니 비겁하오!
How absurd, to call a thief cowardly! I'll take the ornament nonetheless!
도둑에게 비겁하다니 가소롭기 짝이 없군! 금장식은 가져가겠다!
That will not happen no matter what-dasu!
절대 그러지 못할 것이오!
Using smokescreen is the sign of ultimate cowardliness-dasu!
연막을 쓰다니 이 얼마나 비겁한 놈이오!
As I promised, I'm taking the gold ornament!
약속대로 금장식은 가져가신다!
Stop right there-dasu!
멈추시오!
This worked well-dasu.
잘 됐소.
Are you sure about that, Musashi?! Wait for the stormy latter half!
그대로 괜찮겠느냐, 무사시! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
What?! You replaced the ornaments?!
뭐야? 금장식을 바꿔챘다고?!
That's right-dasu! I replaced the ones next to the toilet with the real one-dasu!
그렇소! 화장실 옆 방에 있는 것하고 진품하고 바꾸어 두었소!
You idiot! Those were the real ones!
바보야! 그게 진짜였다!
The ornaments in that room were the real ones that I've replaced!
저 방에 있는 장식이야말로 내가 바꿔친 진품이었다!
Um, Kojirō replaced the real ones and fake ones...
어, 코지로가 진짜하고 가짜를 바꾸고...
and I replaced the fake ones to the real ones...
내가 가짜를 진짜로 바꾸고...
That means the stolen one is the one I've replaced...
그러니까, 훔쳐진 건 내가 바꾼 거니까...
The real ones and fake ones are...
진짜는 가짜하고...
You blockhead! Just look, Musashi!
에이, 답답한 놈! 봐라, 무사시!
It's all over.
이제 끝이다.
Leaves no choice...
이제는...
Lord! Don't even think about it!
영주님! 자결해서는 안 됩니다!
I, Shunnosuke, will take the ornaments back no matter what!
금장식은 이 슌노스케가 목숨을 걸고라서도 되찾아 보이겠습니다!
If you're willing to get those back, then we're going too.
금장식을 되찾으러 갈 거라면 우리도 가겠어.
N- no way! I cannot let something bad happen to Senhime!
그, 그런! 센히메 님을 위험에 처하게 할 순 없습니다!
No, it's alright. It's partially our responsibility too.
아니, 괜찮아. 훔쳐진 건 우리 책임도 있어.
Right, Musashi?!
그치, 무사시?!
Y- yessir-dasu.
그, 그렇소.
But...
그래도...
Please. Take me with you. Let me be with you.
부탁이야. 데려가 줘. 네 옆을 지키게 해 줘.
My small chest is gonna be crushed.
내 작은 가슴이 찌부러져버릴 거야.
Help me-dasu!
으악, 살려주시오!
I'm scared-dasu!
무섭소!
I have a fear of heights-dasu!
나, 고소공포증이오!
Hey! Quit being a scaredy cat and use your eyes to look for Goemondo's hideout!
야! 벌벌 떨고 있지만 말고 정신 차리고 눈 열고 고에몬도의 아지트를 찾아라!
It's all your fault that it got stolen!
훔쳐진 건 죄다 니 책임이니까!
Whatever you say, what's scary is scary-dasu!
그런 말을 해도 무서운 건 무섭소!
I can't see-dasu!
안 보이오!
Hey, I found it-dasu!
아, 찾았소!
Keep in mind that we don't know what kind of contraption is installed here, so please be careful.
잘 들으세요. 어떤 장치가 있을 지 모르니 충분히 조심해 주세요.
Oh, what is this rope for-dasu?
오, 이 줄은 뭣이오?
I just said to be careful!
조심하라고 말했는데!
Sneaking into a house of thief was outrageous!
도둑집에 몰래 들어오다니 거 아주 천번은 괘씸한 놈들이구나!
Now, what should I do to you?
어떻게 해 주실까나.
Hey! Goemondo! Give the stolen ornament back-dasu!
야! 고에몬도! 훔친 금장식을 돌려주시오!
You idiot! There is an end to sands by a seashore, but there is no end to seeds of thieves!
멍청한 놈! 해변의 잔모래가 없어지더라도 세상에 도둑의 씨앗은 없어지지 않으리!
Everything in this world belongs to Goemondo!
이 세상에 있는 모든 것은 고에몬도 님의 것이다!
What are you planning to do with that stolen ornament?!
금장식 따위를 훔쳐서 어쩔 셈이냐!
If you want to know, then let me tell you!
알고 싶다면 말씀해 드려야지!
-I don't want to know-dasu! -Err
-알고 싶지 않소! -어라
But I'll listen just because you're pitiful-dasu.
그래도 불쌍하니까 들어는 주겠소.
Thank you very much.
매우 고맙소이다.
I can't see-dasu!
안 보이오!
What a sightly sight! This pure gold statue fits perfectly for Goemondo, the number one grand thief of Jipangu!
절경이군, 절경이야! 이것이야말로 천하의 고에몬도 님에게 어울리는 순금 전신상이다.
The work had to be delayed because there wasn't enough materials, but with this much gold, it's as if already completed!
지금까지는 재료가 부족해서 작업이 느려졌지만 이만큼의 금이 있다면 이미 완성된 것이나 마찬가지다!
What?! Are you planning to melt the ornament?!
뭐야? 금장식을 녹일 생각인가?!
That's right!
그게 맞다!
You bastard! I won't let that ever happen!
네이놈, 그러도록 냅둘까보냐!
Oh, if those are so valuable, then let me include you into the molten gold from the ornament!
호오, 그렇게나 소중한 장식이라면 녹인 금에 너희들을 같이 굳혀 드릴까나!
I don't want that! I am Senhime, the granddaughter of General Ieyasu! I'm ordering you!
그런 거 싫어! 난 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀, 센히메다! 네게 명령한다!
Untie this rope right now!
이 줄을 바로 풀어라!
Hmph, it doesn't matter if you're a granddaughter of General Ieyasu or grandfailure!
흥, 제너럴 이에야스의 손녀든 효자손이든 관계 없다! 그 이 장소를 안 이상 살아서 돌아갈 수는 없을 테니 말이지!
Huh? Oh, aren't you Karakuri Owl?
어? 오, 이건 카라쿠리 부엉이 아닌가.
Let's see. Kidnap Senhime right away?
응? 어디 보자. 곧장 센히메를 유괴해 오라?
What a coincidence! Good things do follow bad things!
오, 이건 우연이군, 우연이야! 나쁜 일을 하고 있어도 좋은 일이 되기도 하네!
Spare my life! I don't want to die-dasu!
으악, 살려주시오! 죽고 싶지 않소!
A great martial artist knows when to go! Be quiet! It's not like you can live!
멋진 무예가는 단념할 땐 깔끔하게! 조용히 해라! 살 수 있을 것 같냐!
But still, my pride cannot forgive becoming a statue when I'm bound!
그래도 결박된 채로 동상이 되는 건 내 프라이드가 용서하지 못한다!
Make a great-looking statue out of me!
어떻게든 멋진 포즈로 만들어 줘!
Hmph! You should be thankful with becoming gold statues when you're nothing more than little brats!
흥! 너희같은 애송이가 금상이 된다는 것만으로도 고마운 줄 알아라!
Damn it. How mortifying.
젠장, 무념이다.
Soon, everyone, I'm going to save all of you.
좀만 기다려, 모두. 지금 구해줄 테니까.
This is the last resort.
이렇게 된 바 최후의 수단이야.
We're saved-dasu...
살았소...
Princess! Do not interfere!
공주! 방해하면 안 된다!
What a naughty princess! I must give you a punishment.
이 무슨 장난꾸러기 공주구나! 벌을 주어야만 하겠어.
You're the one who's going to receive punishment!
벌을 받는 건 네 쪽이오!
How dare you try to make us into statues-dasu?! Unforgivable-dasu!
잘도 우리를 동상으로 만들려고 했겠소! 용서할 수 없소!
I must pay this back too, for making a fool out of me!
내가 꼴사나운 모습을 보이게 하다니 이 은혜는 어떻게든 갚아 주어야겠어!
Hmph! You're 100 years and 3 days too early to take me down!
흥! 날 쓰러뜨리기에는 100년하고도 3일은 모자르다!
Goegoemondo Almond...
고에고에몬도 아몬드...
Go! Crush those tiny brats flat!
이랴! 저 꼬맹이들을 밟아 부수어 줘라!
Good job, Kojirō!
잘 했어, 코지로!
You are excellent!
훌륭하십니다!
Hmph, right when I was about to take care of him with my dual blades...
쳇, 마침 내가 이도류로 끝내주겠다고 생각하고 있었더니...
Huh?
어?
What is going on-dasu?
어라, 어떻게 된 일이오?
That is no way taking my giant centipede down!
겨우 그런 걸로 쓰러질 거대 지네가 아니다!
Get rid of them!
자, 해치워라!
If you get stung with that poisoned needle, ah! and you'll be dead!
그 독바늘에 찔리면 앗 소리내다 죽는다?
At this rate, I'll be done for-dasu!
이대로는 당하고 마오!
I use dual blades-dasu!
에잇, 난 이도류이오!
I finally opened my eyes towards dual blades.
나, 이도류를 개안했소.
What?! Curse you!
뭐야?! 네이놈, 꼬맹아!
Chink in the armor!
빈틈이다!
That's Kojirō I know!
역시 코지로!
Musashi, you are the one to be praised, for opening your eyes towards dual blades.
무사시야말로 드디어 이도류를 개안했구나.
I'm embarrassed-dasu!
수줍소!
-Everything worked out well, Shunnosuke. -Right.
-잘 됐네요, 슌노스케 씨. -예.
Thank you, Senhime. We now have a great ornament thanks to you, princess.
감사합니다, 센히메 님. 공주님 덕분에 훌륭한 장식이 완성되었습니다.
It's nothing! I wouldn't say that I helped you for a reward.
별 거 아니야! 보답을 바란다고는 절대 말하지는 않을 테니까.
Oh, right. To show our gratitude, we'd like to give you anything you want.
아, 그렇군요. 모든 것에 대한 보답으로 공주님이 원하시는 것을 뭐든 드리고 싶습니다.
Is anything alright? Then I'd like to have Shunnosuke as...
뭐든 좋아? 그럼 나 슌노스케 씨를 저...
Hey.
오.
A father?
아버지?
Congratulations, dear.
여보, 축하드려요.
Thank you, Kazue.
고마워, 카즈에.
No way...
이게 무슨...
So, Senhime, how would you want Shunnosuke?
그래서 센히메 님, 슌노스케 씨를 저 다음엔 무엇입니까?
Oh, that... I mean that to have Shunnosuke's wife as...
아, 그게, 그러니까 슌노스케 씨 부인을, 그러니까...
Oh, right! Have Shunnosuke and his wife to receive rewards!
아, 맞아! 슌노스케 씨하고 부인에게 포상을 준다는 거지!
Never mind.
이제 됐어.
Don't cry like that-dasu. Something good will happen soon after all that-dasu.
그렇게 울지 마시오. 그 일이 있은 이상 어떻게든 좋은 일이 일어날 것이오.
That's right! They say that leftovers will be more fortunate than others.
그렇습니다! 옛날부터 남겨진 자에게는 복이 있다고 하지 않습니까.
Leftover? Kojirō, are you saying that I'm a leftover?!
남겨진 자? 코지로, 내가 나머지라고 말하는 거야?!
N- no, I didn't mean that...
아, 아니, 그런 의미가...
Yeah, I am a leftover after all!
그래, 어차피 난 나머지다!
Stop!
멈춰!
He finally developed the technique of dual blades boasting a fearsome potency.
결국에 가공할 위력을 가진 이도류를 완성했다.
Keep it up, Musashi! Become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
힘내라, 무사시! 지팡구 넘버원의 무예가가 되어라!
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
We meet Baiken once again, and he got a job of guard.
경비로 취직한 바이켄하고의 재회도 순간.
The feudal lord seems to be having trouble with a monster Nue.
영주님이 요괴 누에에게 시달리고 하오.
For our friendship, I must act to help, or it would bringing shame upon myself-dasu!
이렇게 된 바 우정을 위해 발벗고 나서지 않으면 사내의 체면이 떨어지오!
We join to get rid of that Nue-dasu, and Onihime is behind!
누에 퇴치에 뛰어들었는데 그 뒤에 오니히메의 모습이!
Next story! The Night that Nue Cries is Scary-dasu.
다음 이야기! 누에가 우는 밤은 무섭소
It's the stormy power of friendship-dasu!
질풍노도의 우정파워이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
The Night that
누에가 우는 밤은 무섭소
Nue Cries is Scary
기대하세요!